let games =[
    [
     {
       question: "Who won the 2018 FIFA World Cup?",
       choiceA: "France",
       choiceB: "Brazil",
       choiceC: "Germany",
       choiceD: "Spain",
       correct: "A",
     },{
        question: "In what year was the first world cup held?",
        choiceA: "1966",
        choiceB: "1930",
        choiceC: "1902",
        choiceD: "1890",
        correct: "B",
      },{
        question: "Which nation has won the most World Cups?",
        choiceA: "Argentina",
        choiceB: "Germany",
        choiceC: "Brazil",
        choiceD: "England",
        correct: "C",
      },{
        question: "What was the first World Cup trophy called?",
        choiceA: "Jules Rimet Trophy",
        choiceB: "Coup du Monde",
        choiceC: "Victory",
        choiceD: "Coupe des Clubs Champions",
        correct: "A",
      },{
        question: "Who is the all-time leading World Cup goalscorer?",
        choiceA: "Miroslav Close",
        choiceB: "Diego Maradona",
        choiceC: "Ronaldo(From Brazil)",
        choiceD: "Ronaldo(From Portugal)",
        correct: "A",
      },{
        question: "What musical instrument was banned by FIFA after the 2010 World Cup?",
        choiceA: "Guitar",
        choiceB: "Drum",
        choiceC: "Vuvuzela",
        choiceD: "Harmonica",
        correct: "C",
      },{
        question: "Who won the first World Cup?",
        choiceA: "Brazil",
        choiceB: "England",
        choiceC: "The Soviet Union",
        choiceD: "Uruguay",
        correct: "D",
      },{
        question: "Which nation is the only one to top the FIFA World Rankings without ever winning a World Cup?",
        choiceA: "USA",
        choiceB: "Mexico",
        choiceC: "Russia",
        choiceD: "Belgium",
        correct: "D",
      },{
        question: "In what year was the first FIFA Womens World Cup held?",
        choiceA: "2001",
        choiceB: "1942",
        choiceC: "1991",
        choiceD: "2011",
        correct: "C",
      },{
        question: "Which nation was the first Asian country to reach the World Cup semi-finals in 2002?",
        choiceA: "China",
        choiceB: "South Korea",
        choiceC: "Japan",
        choiceD: "North Korea",
        correct: "B",
      },{
        question: "Before Qatar 2022, how many nations have won the FIFA World Cup?",
        choiceA: "8",
        choiceB: "11",
        choiceC: "13",
        choiceD: "19",
        correct: "A",
      },{
        question: "Which player scored a record 13 goals in a single tournament?",
        choiceA: "Liam Brady",
        choiceB: "Diego Maradona",
        choiceC: "Pele",
        choiceD: "Just Fontaine",
        correct: "D",
      },{
        question: "What nation has on the most World Cup tournaments with a total of 5?",
        choiceA: "Argentina",
        choiceB: "Germany",
        choiceC: "Brazil",
        choiceD: "Italy",
        correct: "C",
      },{
        question: "What nation has lost the most World Cup finals with 4 losses?",
        choiceA: "Germany",
        choiceB: "England",
        choiceC: "Netherlands",
        choiceD: "Spain",
        correct: "A",
      },{
        question: "Where was the first ever world cup held?",
        choiceA: "Switzerland",
        choiceB: "Uruguay",
        choiceC: "Sweden",
        choiceD: "Mexico",
        correct: "B",
      },{
        question: "Which nation will have its World Cup debut in 2022?",
        choiceA: "Qutar",
        choiceB: "Saudi Arabia",
        choiceC: "Senegal",
        choiceD: "Japan",
        correct: "A",
      },{
        question: "Who will host the 2026 tournament?",
        choiceA: "Portugal and Spain",
        choiceB: "Britian and Ireland",
        choiceC: "North Korea and South Korea",
        choiceD: "USA, Mexico, Canada",
        correct: "D",
      },{
        question: "Prior to Qatar 2022, what nation has scored the most world cup goals with 236?",
        choiceA: "Italy",
        choiceB: "France",
        choiceC: "Brazil",
        choiceD: "Germany",
        correct: "C",
      },{
        question: "Prior to Qatar 2022, what nation has lost the most games at World Cup tournaments with 28 losses?",
        choiceA: "Spain",
        choiceB: "USA",
        choiceC: "England",
        choiceD: "Mexico",
        correct: "D",
      },{
        question: "Prior to Qatar 2022, what nation has concided the most goals at World cup tournaments with a total of 130?",
        choiceA: "Brazil",
        choiceB: "France",
        choiceC: "Brazil",
        choiceD: "Germany",
        correct: "D",
      },{
        question: "What nation has made it to the most tournament finals without winning, losing 3 times?",
        choiceA: "Croatia",
        choiceB: "Czech",
        choiceC: "Netherlands",
        choiceD: "Hungary",
        correct: "C",
      },{
        question: "How many teams will play at the 2026 World Cup?",
        choiceA: "32",
        choiceB: "38",
        choiceC: "42",
        choiceD: "48",
        correct: "D",
      },{
        question: "How much money did Qatar reported spend to host the 2022 tournament?",
        choiceA: "$300 Billion",
        choiceB: "$30 Billion",
        choiceC: "$3 Billion",
        choiceD: "$300 Million",
        correct: "A",
      },
    ]